Guide to the University of Utah football video collection 1948-1999
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Coach's films: defense, 1977-1980 (Box 24a)
  - Utah vs. BYU Q1-Q3, undated; 16mm film (Reel 535-537)
- Coach's films: kicking, 1977-1981 (Box 24b)
  - Utah vs. Oklahoma kicking, 1977 September 01; 16mm film (Reel 538)
  - Utah vs. Houston kicking, 1977 September 24; 16mm film (Reel 539)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1977 October 01; 16mm film (Reel 540)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1977 October 08; 16mm film (Reel 541)
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1977 October 15; 16mm film (Reel 542)
  - Utah vs. Arizona kicking, 1977 October 22; 16mm film (Reel 543)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State kicking, 1977 October 27; 16mm film (Reel 544)
  - Utah vs. BYU kicking, 1977 November 05; 16mm film (Reel 545)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1977 November 12; 16mm film (Reel 546)
  - Utah vs. Florida kicking, 1977 November 19; 16mm film (Reel 547)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1977 November 26; 16mm film (Reel 548)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State kicking, 1978 September 09; 16mm film (Reel 549)
  - Utah vs. Houston kicking, 1978 September 23; 16mm film (Reel 550)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1978 September 30; 16mm film (Reel 551)
  - Utah vs. Iowa kicking, 1978 October 06; 16mm film (Reel 552)
  - Utah vs. Weber State kicking, 1978 October 14; 16mm film (Reel 553)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1978 October 21; 16mm film (Reel 554)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1978 November 04; 16mm film (Reel 555)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1978 November 11; 16mm film (Reel 556)
  - Utah vs.UNLV kicking, 1980 September 20; 16mm film (Reel 557)
  - Utah vs.Colorado State kicking, 1980 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 558)
  - place-kicking, extra points, field goals, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 559)
  - Utah vs.BYU ground level, 1978; 16mm film (Reel 560)
  - Kickoff returns, 1977; 16mm film (Reel 561)
- Coach's films: highlights, kicking, plays, 1977-1984 (Box 25)
  - Tony Lindsay highlights, 1977-1980; 16mm film (Reel 562-563)
    Running back
  - Rob Richeson highlights, 1977-1981; 16mm film (Reel 564)
  - Power I plays, 1977-1978; 16mm film (Reel 565)
  - Ram G sweep, 1977-1981; 16mm film (Reel 566)
  - Delays: fullbacks, halfbacks, tight ends, 1977-1978; 16mm film (Reel 567)
  - Draws, 1977-1981; 16mm film (Reel 568)
  - Play action passes, 1977-1982; 16mm film (Reel 569)
  - Slip screens, 1977-1983; 16mm film (Reel 570)
  - Steve Folsom highlights, 1978-1980; 16mm film (Reel 571)
    Tight end
  - Del Rodgers highlights, 1979-1981; 16mm film (Reel 572-573)
  - Counters, 1980 August 23; 16mm film (Reel 574)
  - Pop: a counter/trap, circa 1981; 16mm film (Reel 575)
  - 26-27 power: Lindsay, Rogers, Walker, Richeson, Monroe, undated; 16mm film (Reel 576)
  - place-kick defense: fire, extra points, field goals, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 577)
  - Sweeps, pitches, 1981-1983; 16mm film (Reel 578)
  - Sweep screen and related plays, undated; 16mm film (Reel 579)
  - Spring defense: run, 43 regular, stack, undated; 16mm film (Reel 580)
  - Utah special teams: place-kick defense, 1983; 16mm film (Reel 581)
  - Utah special teams: place-kick field goals, extra points, 1983; 16mm film (Reel 582)
  - Utah special teams: punt returns, 1983; 16mm film (Reel 583)
  - Utah special teams: kick-off returns, 1983; 16mm film (Reel 584)
  - Scrimmage kicking, 1983 August 26; 16mm film (Reel 585)
  - Punts, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 586)
    Possibly from Utah vs. Hawaii (10/20/84)
  - Kickoffs, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 587)
    Possibly from Utah vs. Wyoming (9/29/84)
  - Kicking, 1984 August 23; 16mm film (Reel 588)
  - Stack cover 3, run, good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 589)
- Coach's films: kicking, 1979 (Box 26)
  - Utah vs. Long Beach State kicking, 1979 September 01; 16mm film (Reel 590)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1979 September 08; 16mm film (Reel 591)
  - Utah vs. Washington kicking, 1979 September 15; 16mm film (Reel 592)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee kicking, 1979 September 22; 16mm film (Reel 593)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee defense, 1979 September 22; 16mm film (Reel 594)
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1979 September 29; 16mm film (Reel 595)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1979 October 06; 16mm film (Reel 596)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1979 October 13; 16mm film (Reel 597)
  - Utah vs. UNLV kicking, 1979 October 20; 16mm film (Reel 598)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1979 October 27; 16mm film (Reel 599)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1979 November 03; 16mm film (Reel 600)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1979 November 10; 16mm film (Reel 601)
  - Utah vs. BYU kicking, 1979 November 17; 16mm film (Reel 602-603)
    Duplicate reels
- Coach's films: highlights and plays, 1979-1983 (Box 27)
  - Dropbacks II, 1979-1981; 16mm film (Reel 604)
  - Jim Teahan highlights, 1978-1981; 16mm film (Reel 605-606)
    Wide receiver
  - Hilria Johnson highlights, 1980-1981; 16mm film (Reel 607)
  - Danny Tarver highlights, 1980-1983; 16mm film (Reel 608)
    Full back
    Includes some Timmy Tarver highlights
- Coach's films: kicking, 1978; 1980 (Box 28)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1978 December 02; 16mm film (Reel 609-610)
  - Utah vs. Boise State kicking, 1980 September 06; 16mm film (Reel 611)
  - Utah vs. Nebraska kicking, 1980 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 612)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State kicking, 1980 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 613)
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1980 October 04; 16mm film (Reel 614)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1980 October 11; 16mm film (Reel 615)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1980 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 616)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1980 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 617)
  - Utah vs. BYU kicking, 1980 November 22; 16mm film (Reel 618)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1980 November 29; 16mm film (Reel 619)
  - SWP 4 pitch, 1980; 16mm film (Reel 620)
- Coach's films: plays and games, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Punt returns: fake punts/fire, returns, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 621)
  - Punt returns: fair caught, touchbacks, out of bounds, downed, punt blocks attempted, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 622)
  - Kickoffs: touchbacks, returns, squibs, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 623)
  - Punts: blocked, returned, downed, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 624)
  - Punts: out of bounds, fair caught, touchbacks, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 625)
  - Kickoff returns: returns, onside prevent returns, touchbacks, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 626)
  - Slants, cuts, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 627)
  - Defense: pass, 4/3 regular, stack, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 628)
  - Boots, waggles, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 629)
  - 3 step passes, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 630)
  - Miscellaneous kicks, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 631)
  - Okie cover 2, run, good and bad, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 632)
  - ISO, lead, 1981; 16mm film (Reel 633)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1981 September 05; 16mm film (Reel 634)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1981 September 05; 16mm film (Reel 635)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1981 September 12; 16mm film (Reel 636-637)
  - Utah vs. Northwestern defense, 1981 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 638)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1981 October 17; 16mm film (Reel 639)
  - Utah vs. UNLV defense, 1981 October 24; 16mm film (Reel 640-641)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1981 November 07; 16mm film (Reel 642-643)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1981 November 14; 16mm film (Reel 644-645)
- Coach's films: plays and games, 1981-1982 (Box 30)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1981 November 21; 16mm film (Reel 646-647)
  - Scrimmage kicking, 1982 August 27; 16mm film (Reel 648)
  - Place kick defense: blocked kicks, opponents' extra points, opponents' field goals, 1982; 16mm film (Reel 649)
  - Punts: punt blocked/fire, returns left, right and middle, 1982; 16mm film (Reel 650)
  - Punts: out of bounds kicks, fair catches, kicks downed, touchbacks, 1982; 16mm film (Reel 651)
  - Kickoffs: touchbacks, returns, squibs, 1982; 16mm film (Reel 652)
  - Place-kicks: extra points, field goals, 1982; 16mm film (Reel 653)
  - Kickoff returns: returns to left, middle and right, onsite and prevent returns, touchbacks, 1982; 16mm film (Reel 654)
  - Opponent punts: fakes and fires, returns, 1982; 16mm film (Reel 655)
  - Opponent punts: fair catches, touchbacks, out of bounds kicks, punts downed by opponents, punt blocks attempted, 1982; 16mm film (Reel 656)
  - Options: runs and passes, 1982; 16mm film (Reel 657)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1982 September 11; 16mm film (Reel 658)
  - Utah vs. Texas offense, 1982 September 18; 16mm film (Reel 659-660)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1982 October 01; 16mm film (Reel 661-662)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1982 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 663-664)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1982 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 665-666)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1982 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 667)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1982 October 30; 16mm film (Reel 668)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1982 November 06; 16mm film (Reel 669-670)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1982 November 20; 16mm film (Reel 671-672)
- Coach's films: games and highlights, 1982-1984 (Box 31)
  - Fake punts and point returns vs. Air Force, punt drills, 1983-1984; 16mm film (Reel 673)
  - Kickoffs, 1983; 16mm film (Reel 674-675)
  - Punts, 1983; 16mm film (Reel 676-677)
  - Punt returns, 1983; 16mm film (Reel 678)
  - Hilria Johnson highlights, 1982-1983; 16mm film (Reel 679)
  - Goal line offense, 1983 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 680)
  - Kicking, 1983 August 25; 16mm film (Reel 681)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1983 September 03; 16mm film (Reel 682-683)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico special teams, 1983 September 03; 16mm film (Reel 684-685)
  - Utah vs. Arizona defense, 1983 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 686-687)
  - Utah vs. Arizona kicking, 1983 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 688-689)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1983 September 17; 16mm film (Reel 690-691)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1983 September 17; 16mm film (Reel 692)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1983 September 24; 16mm film (Reel 693-694)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1983 October 01; 16mm film (Reel 695-696)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1983 October 01; 16mm film (Reel 697)
- Coach's films: games, 1983 (Box 32)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1983 October 01; 16mm film (Reel 698)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1983 October 08; 16mm film (Reel 699-700)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1983 October 08; 16mm film (Reel 701-702)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1983 October 15; 16mm film (Reel 703-704)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1983 October 15; 16mm film (Reel 705)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1983 October 22; 16mm film (Reel 706-707)
  - Utah vs. Air Force kicking, 1983 October 22; 16mm film (Reel 708-709)
  - Utah vs. California State Fullerton (CSF) kicking, 1983 November 05; 16mm film (Reel 710)
  - Utah vs. CSF defense, 1983 November 05; 16mm film (Reel 711-712)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1983 November 12; 16mm film (Reel 713-714)
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1983 November 12; 16mm film (Reel 715)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1983 November 19; 16mm film (Reel 716-718)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1983 November 19; 16mm film (Reel 719-721)
  - Utah vs. BYU kicking, 1983 November 19; 16mm film (Reel 719)
- Coach's films: plays and practices, 1984; 1987 (Box 33)
  - Front blitz, run and pass, good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 720)
  - Pass scrambles, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 721)
  - G.L. run and pass good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 722)
  - Utah vs. BYU Thursday practice offense, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 723)
  - E 3 cover vs. run good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 724)
  - Slant run good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 725)
  - Wish bone pass good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 726)
  - Big plays, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 727)
  - 62/60 jet run pass, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 728)
  - Wish bone whip side drive, opt arc good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 729)
  - Stack cover 2 good and bad run, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 730)
  - Wish bone eagle side good and bad, veer G load, veer G arc, counter power trap, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 731)
  - Slant vs. pass good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 732)
  - Secondary blitz run good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 733)
  - Wish bone whip side drive opt load, veer G arc, load, counter, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 734)
  - Unbalanced reach load option, eagle, first whip 20 base load option, 1984 March 17; 16mm film (Reel 735)
  - Stack cover 3 pass good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 736)
  - Stack cover 2 pass good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 737)
  - Pass rush, sacks, hurries, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 738)
  - Okie cover 3, run and bad, good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 739)
  - Utah vs. Weber State kicking, 1984 September 01; 16mm film (Reel 740-741)
- Coach's films: games, 1984 (Box 34)
  - Utah vs. Weber State offense, 1984 September 01; 16mm film (Reel 742-745)
  - Utah vs. Weber State defense, 1984 September 01; 16mm film (Reel 746-749)
  - Utah vs. Washington State offense, 1984 September 08; 16mm film (Reel 750-751)
  - Utah vs. Washington State defense, 1984 September 08; 16mm film (Reel 752-755)
  - Utah vs. Washington State kicking, 1984 September 08; 16mm film (Reel 756)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee kicking, 1984 September 15; 16mm film (Reel 757-758)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee offense, 1984 September 15; 16mm film (Reel 759-760)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee defense, 1984 September 15; 16mm film (Reel 761-765)
    Reels 1-2, 1-2, 2-2, 2-2, 2-2
- Coach's films: games, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee defense, 1984 September 15; 16mm film (Reel 766)
  - Utah vs. Air Force kicking, 1984 September 22; 16mm film (Reel 767-769)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1984 September 22; 16mm film (Reel 770-773)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1984 September 29; 16mm film (Reel 774-777)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1984 September 29; 16mm film (Reel 778-781)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1984 September 29; 16mm film (Reel 782-783)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1984 October 05; 16mm film (Reel 784-787)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1984 October 05; 16mm film (Reel 788-790)
- Coach's films: games, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1984 October 05; 16mm film (Reel 791)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1984 October 05; 16mm film (Reel 792-795)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1984 October 13; 16mm film (Reel 796-797)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1984 October 13; 16mm film (Reel 798-801)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1984 October 13; 16mm film (Reel 802-805)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1984 October 20; 16mm film (Reel 806-809)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1984 October 20; 16mm film (Reel 810-812)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1984 October 20; 16mm film (Reel 813-814)
- Coach's films: games, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1984 October 20; 16mm film (Reel 815)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1984 October 20; 16mm film (Reel 816-817)
    Possibly duplicates
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1984 October 27; 16mm film (Reel 818-821)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1984 October 27; 16mm film (Reel 822-825)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1984 October 27; 16mm film (Reel 826-829)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1984 November 03; 16mm film (Reel 830-833)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1984 November 03; 16mm film (Reel 834-835)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1984 November 03; 16mm film (Reel 836-838)
- Coach's films: games, 1984 (Box 38)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1984 November 03; 16mm film (Reel 839)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1984 November 03; 16mm film (Reel 840-841)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1984 November 10; 16mm film (Reel 842)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1984 November 10; 16mm film (Reel 843-846)
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1984 November 10; 16mm film (Reel 847-850)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1984 November 19; 16mm film (Reel 851-854)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1984 November 19; 16mm film (Reel 855-856)
  - Utah vs. BYU kicking, 1984 November 19; 16mm film (Reel 857-860)
  - Utah cover 3, bad, 1984 November 19; 16mm film (Reel 861)
- Coach's films: plays and practices, 1984-1988 (Box 39)
  - Blood vs. pass good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 862)
  - Okie cover 2 pass good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 863)
  - Blood vs. run good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 864)
  - Wish bone eagle side dive opt arc good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 865)
  - Cover 3 pass good, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 866)
  - Nickel and 34 defense vs. run and pass good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 867)
  - Secondary blitz pass good and bad, 1984; 16mm film (Reel 868)
  - Rifle, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 869)
  - Screens, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 870)
  - Linebacker trainer, inside plays, 1986 March 06; 16mm film (Reel 871)
  - Blast, center drive, trap, draw, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 872)
  - Kicking, 1986 August 30; 16mm film (Reel 873)
  - 7 on 7, 1987 April 22; 16mm film (Reel 874)
  - Team, 1987 April 22; 16mm film (Reel 875)
  - Spring scrimmage, 1987 April 29; 16mm film (Reel 876)
  - Screens, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 877)
  - Rifle, strike, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 878)
  - Spring regular/green vs. run, 1988; 16mm film (Reel 879)
  - Pup, 1988 April 15; 16mm film (Reel 880)
  - Scrum, 1988 April 26; 16mm film (Reel 881)
  - 7 on 7, 1988 May 03; 16mm film (Reel 882)
  - Spring football 2-3, 1988 May 03; 16mm film (Reel 883-884)
  - Pup, zone, 1988 May 03; 16mm film (Reel 885)
  - Team 2, April 21; 16mm film (Reel 886)
  - FLs, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 887)
  - Interceptions, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 888)
- Coach's films: games, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Special teams: extra points, field goals, 1985; 16mm film (Reel 889)
  - Special teams: kickoff returns, 1985; 16mm film (Reel 890-891)
  - Special teams: punts, 1985; 16mm film (Reel 892-893)
  - Special teams: kickoffs, 1985; 16mm film (Reel 894-895)
  - Special teams: punt returns, 1985; 16mm film (Reel 896-897)
  - Place-kick defense: extra points, field goals, 1985; 16mm film (Reel 898)
  - Utah vs. Boise State offense, 1985 September 07; 16mm film (Reel 899-901)
  - Utah vs. Boise State defense, 1985 September 07; 16mm film (Reel 902-906)
    Reels 1-2, 1-2, 1-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Boise State kicking, 1985 September 07; 16mm film (Reel 907-908)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1985 September 14; 16mm film (Reel 909-910)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1985 September 14; 16mm film (Reel 911-912)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1985 September 14; 16mm film (Reel 913)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1985 September 14; 16mm film (Reel 914-915)
    Possibly not actually Utah vs. Hawaii
- Coach's films: games, 1985 (Box 41)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1985 September 14; 16mm film (Reel 916-917)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1985 September 14; 16mm film (Reel 918-919)
  - Utah vs. Washington State offense, 1985 September 21; 16mm film (Reel 920-921)
  - Utah vs. Washington State defense, 1985 September 21; 16mm film (Reel 922-924)
  - Utah vs. Washington State kicking, 1985 September 21; 16mm film (Reel 925)
  - Utah vs. Washington State 40 draw, 1985 September 21; 16mm film (Reel 926)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1985 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 927-930)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1985 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 931-934)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1985 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 935-937)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1985 October 04; 16mm film (Reel 938-940)
- Coach's films: games, 1985 (Box 42)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1985 October 04; 16mm film (Reel 941-944)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1985 October 04; 16mm film (Reel 945-948)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, 1985 October 12; 16mm film (Reel 949-950)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1985 October 12; 16mm film (Reel 951-954)
    Reels 1-2, 1-1, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Arizona State kicking, 1985 October 12; 16mm film (Reel 955-956)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1985 October 19; 16mm film (Reel 957-961)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1985 October 19; 16mm film (Reel 962-963)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1985 October 19; 16mm film (Reel 964)
- Coach's films: games, 1985 (Box 43)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1985 October 19; 16mm film (Reel 965)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1985 October 26; 16mm film (Reel 966-968)
    Reel 1-2, 1-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1985 October 26; 16mm film (Reel 969-970)
    Reel 1-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Air Force kicking, 1985 October 26; 16mm film (Reel 971-972)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1985 November 02; 16mm film (Reel 973-976)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1985 November 02; 16mm film (Reel 977-979)
    Reel 1-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1985 November 02; 16mm film (Reel 980-981)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1985 November 09; 16mm film (Reel 982-985)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1985 November 09; 16mm film (Reel 986-988)
- Coach's films: games, 1985 (Box 44)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1985 November 09; 16mm film (Reel 989-990)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1985 November 16; 16mm film (Reel 991-994)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1985 November 16; 16mm film (Reel 995-998)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State: Colorado State's defense, 1985 November 16; 16mm film (Reel 999-1000)
    From Colorado State athletics
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1985 November 16; 16mm film (Reel 1001-1002)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1985 November 23; 16mm film (Reel 1003-1006)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1985 November 23; 16mm film (Reel 1007-1012)
    Reel 1-3, 1-3, 2-3, 2-3, 3-3, 3-3
  - Utah vs. BYU kicking, 1985 November 23; 16mm film (Reel 1013-1014)
  - Errol Tucker return highlights, 1984-1985; 16mm film (Reel 1015)
- Coach's films: plays, practice and highlights, 1986 (Box 45)
  - Linebacker training bear, stack, eagle vs. outside plays, 1986 March 06; 16mm film (Reel 1016)
  - Unidentified film, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1017)
  - Veer arc option, eagle, first and second whip side, 1986 March 17; 16mm film (Reel 1018)
  - Linebacker trainer Okie vs. outside plays, 1986 March 10; 16mm film (Reel 1019)
  - Linebacker trainer, P.A. pass, flow rule, 1986 March 06; 16mm film (Reel 1020)
  - Base arc option, eagle, first and second whip side, 1986 March 17; 16mm film (Reel 1021)
  - Linebacker trainer, blitzes, bullets, rams, stabs, 1986 March 06; 16mm film (Reel 1022)
  - Linebacker trainer Okie vs. inside plays, 1986 March 10; 16mm film (Reel 1023)
  - Linebacker training bear, stack, eagle vs. inside plays, 1986 March 06; 16mm film (Reel 1024)
  - Veer load option, eagle, first whip side, second veer load, crack last, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1025)
  - Veer G load option, eagle, first and second whip side, 1986 March 17; 16mm film (Reel 1026)
  - Fire, dash, scramble, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1027)
  - 27 counter trap, 26 counter, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1028)
  - 26 power, 28 G, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1029)
  - Draws, express, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1030)
  - Sacks, scrambles, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1031)
  - Fumbles, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1032)
  - Key, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1033)
  - 28, 29 quick pitch, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1034)
  - Orange, slash Charlie, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1035)
  - Punts, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1036)
  - Traps, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1037)
  - Options, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1038)
- Coach's films: plays, practice, highlights and games, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Brown, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1039)
  - Interceptions, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1040)
  - Wide screens, 1986 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 1041)
  - Extra plays and field goals, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1042)
  - Place-kick defense, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1043)
  - Strike, fan strike, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1044)
  - Red 434 flat and cross, 389 flat and cross, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1045)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1986 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 1046-1051)
    Reels 1-2, 1-2, 1-2, 2-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1986 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 1052-1057)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1986 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 1058-1069)